[
	{
		"question": "Pilot want to practice fyling the Airplane, Airplane goes to Land and Airplane needs to select right ways! where correct ways for Airplane goes to Land?",
    "fail": "You suck at (✈️)flying practice and Almost crushed but your friend help you",
    "work": "(✈️)Airplane flying practice",
    "amount": 500,
    "correct": "You great as (✈️)Airplane flying practice and earn 500 Moneys",
		"answers": ["right", "r"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Pilot want to practice fyling the Airplane, Airplane goes to Land and Airplane needs to select middle ways! where correct ways for Airplane goes to Land?",
    "fail": "You suck at (✈️)flying practice and Almost crushed but your friend help you",
    "work": "(✈️)Airplane flying practice",
    "amount": 500,
    "correct": "You great as (✈️)Airplane flying practice and earn 500 Moneys",
		"answers": ["middle", "m"]
	},
	{
		"question": "The s needs 100Ml you have 45Ml, How many you need Ml?",
    "work": "(👨‍🍳)Chef",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🍳)Chef and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🍳)Chef and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 250,
    "answers": ["55", "55ml"]
	},
  {
		"question": "Airplane in middle ways, Airplane goes to Miami, Wheres the correct ways goes to Miami? Tips: Miami in left ways",
    "work": "(👨‍✈️)Pilot",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍✈️)Pilot and Airplane crashed you must pay for this!",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍✈️)Pilot and earn 550 Moneys",
    "amount": 550,
    "answers": ["l", "left"]
	},
  {
		"question": "What is code : 34404 607",
    "work": "(👨‍💻)Programmer",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍💻)Programmer and you dont get money to hack the bank",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍💻)Programmer and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 250,
    "answers": ["ERROR BOT", "error bot"]
	},
  {
		"question": "What is code : 1 I0v3 40u",
    "work": "(👨‍💻)Programmer",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍💻)Programmer and you dont get money to hack the bank",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍💻)Programmer and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 250,
    "answers": ["I love you", "i love you"]
	},
  {
		"question": "right <---🏃‍---> left || Where ways goes Robbery?",
    "work": "(👮‍♂️)Policeman",
    "fail": "You suck at (👮‍♂️)Policeman. Robbery has run",
    "correct": "You great as (👮‍♂️)Policeman and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 150,
    "answers": ["r", "right"]
	},
  {
		"question": "The cake needs 75Ml you have 16Ml, How many you need Ml?",
    "work": "(👨‍🍳)Chef",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🍳)Chef and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🍳)Chef and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 250,
    "answers": ["59", "59ml"]
	},
  {
		"question": "The cake needs 100Ml you have 36Ml, How many you need Ml?",
    "work": "(👨‍🍳)Chef",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🍳)Chef and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🍳)Chef and earn 250 Moneys",
    "amount": 250,
    "answers": ["64", "64ml"]
	},
  {
		"question": "2 + 2 x 2 = ?",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 270 Moneys",
    "amount": 270,
    "answers": ["8", "eight"]
	},
  {
		"question": "2 x 68 + 1 x 0 = ?",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 270 Moneys",
    "amount": 270,
    "answers": ["0", "zero"]
	},
  {
		"question": "🔘 🔘 🔘 🔘 🔘| How many orbits on the space?",
    "work": "(👨‍🚀)Atronaut",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🚀)Atronaut and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🚀)Atronaut and earn 800 Moneys",
    "amount": 800,
    "answers": ["5", "five"]
	},
  {
		"question": "what year was Indonesia independent?",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 690 Moneys",
    "amount": 690,
    "answers":["1945"]
	},
  {
		"question": "who president 1st on indonesia",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 695 Moneys",
    "amount": 695,
    "answers": ["Soekarno"]
	},
  {
		"question": "what we get vitamin by eating Orange?",
    "work": "(👨‍🔬)Scientist",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🔬)Scientist and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🔬)Scientist and earn 505 Moneys",
    "amount": 505,
    "answers": ["Vitamin C", "vitamin c", "c", "C"]
	},
  {
		"question": "what president on russia?",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 695 Moneys",
    "amount": 680,
    "answers": ["Vladimir Putin"]
	},
  {
		"question": "how you say hi with speak russia?",
    "work": "(👨‍🏫)Teacher",
    "fail": "You suck at (👨‍🏫)Teacher and you dont earn Money",
    "correct": "You great as (👨‍🏫)Teacher and earn 695 Moneys",
    "amount": 650,
    "answers": ["Privet","привет"]
	}
]